[[
    {
      "setName":"English Words",
      "setId":"english-words",
      "cards":[
        {
          "id":1,
          "question":"Disingenious",
          "answer":"Not candid or sincere by pretending one know less than one actually does"
        },
        {"id":2,"question":"Scrutiny","answer":"Critical Observation"},
        {"id":3,"question":"Assail","answer":"Make a violent attack on"},
        {"id":4,"question":"Eschew","answer":"Deliberately Avoid Using"},
        {"id":5,"question":"Infallible","answer":"Incapable of making mistakes"},
        {
          "id":6,
          "question":"Serendipitous",
          "answer":"Happenning for a good reason"
        },
        {"id":7,"question":"Superflous","answer":"Unnecessary"},
        {"id":8,"question":"Augury","answer":"An Omen"},
        {"id":9,"question":"Asinine","answer":"Stupid"},
        {"id":10,"question":"Abeyance","answer":"In a temporary state of unuse"}
      ]
    },
    {
      "setName":"Japanese Words",
      "setId":"japanese-words",
      "cards":[
        {"id":1,"question":"いしゃ","answer":"Doctor"},
        {"id":2,"question":"へいし","answer":"Soldier"},
        {"id":3,"question":"けんちくか","answer":"Architect"},
        {"id":4,"question":"きょうし","answer":"Teacher"},
        {"id":5,"question":"かしゅ","answer":"Singer"}
      ]
    },
    {
      "setName":"Anime Manga Cards",
      "setId":"anime-manga-cards",
      "cards":[
        {"id":1,"question":"Monster","answer":"Naoki Urasawa"},
        {"id":2,"question":"Berserk","answer":"Kentaro Miura"},
        {
          "id":3,
          "question":"Legend of the Galactic Heores",
          "answer":"Yoshiki Tanaka"
        },
        {"id":4,"question":"Mushishi","answer":"Urashibara Yuki"},
        {"id":5,"question":"20th Century Boys","answer":"Naoki Urasawa"}
      ]
    }
  ],

  [
    {
        "question": "Disingenious",
        "answer": "Not candid or sincere by pretending one know less than one actually does"
    },
    {
        "question": "Scrutiny",
        "answer": "Critical Observation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Assail",
        "answer": "Make a violent attack on"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eschew",
        "answer": "Deliberately Avoid Using"
    },
    {
        "question": "Infallible",
        "answer": "Incapable of making mistakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Serendipitous",
        "answer": "Happenning for a good reason"
    },
    {
        "question": "Superflous",
        "answer": "Unnecessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "Augury",
        "answer": "An Omen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Asinine",
        "answer": "Stupid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Abeyance",
        "answer": "In a temporary state of unuse"
    }
]

,

[
    {
        "question": "Monster",
        "answer": "Naoki Urasawa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Berserk",
        "answer": "Kentaro Miura"
    },
    {
        "question": "Legend of the Galactic Heores",
        "answer": "Yoshiki Tanaka"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mushishi",
        "answer": "Urashibara Yuki"
    },
    {
        "question": "20th Century Boys",
        "answer": "Naoki Urasawa"
    }
]

]